<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The #GrabYourWallet Movement on #GrabYourWallet movement</title>
    <link>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The #GrabYourWallet Movement on #GrabYourWallet movement</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 13:45:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.grabyourwallet.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Actions to Take</title>
      <link>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/actions_to_take/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 13:45:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/actions_to_take/</guid>
      <description>#GrabYourWallet Action Guide The goal of the #GrabYourWallet boycott is to motivate companies to take specific actions to evolve in a more ethical inclusive direction. This is so we can remove them from the boycott list and return as customers as quickly as possible! Over 30 companies have already been removed from the list. Here are some ways you can make sure even more can be removed.
In order of priority:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boycott These Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/boycott_these_companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 13:45:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/boycott_these_companies/</guid>
      <description>.content  ul  li  a {font-weight:600;} .content  ul  li {margin-bottom:30px;} dt {font-weight:600;color:#777;} h2 {color:#333;} h2 {margin-top:40px;padding-top:40px;} h3 {color:#555;padding-top:20px;} dl {border-bottom:10px solid #ececec;padding-bottom:40px;} dt:first-child, dt:last-of-type {float:left;margin-right:10px;}  If you are contacting a company about Trump products / affiliations, here&amp;rsquo;s a sample of what you can say:
 &amp;ldquo;Hi. I’m a customer of [CompanyName]. Unfortunately I can no longer do business with your company because it does business with the Trump family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Coverage</title>
      <link>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/media_coverage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 13:45:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/media_coverage/</guid>
      <description>Major Media Coverage of #GrabYourWallet ABC  Transcript: George Stephanopoulos Interviews Trump Family  The Atlantic  Trump Thanks L.L. Bean, the Latest Retailer Caught Between Him and His Critics Is Donald Trump’s Presidency Hurting His Businesses?  BBC  The Trump resistance movement builds  Bloomberg  Nordstrom Is Cutting Ivanka Trump’s Brand Due to Poor Sales Stores Play Hide and Seek With Ivanka’s Products  Boston Herald  Cashman: Ivanka Trump&amp;rsquo;s brand endangered by derailing train  Business Insider  Anti-NRA activists are calling for a boycott of Amazon, Apple, and FedEx — and it could be huge An anti-Trump movement is calling for the boycott of these 32 retailers Nordstrom responds to viral letter calling on retailer to drop Ivanka Trump&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;toxic&amp;rsquo; brand The anti-Trump boycott of 50 retailers won&amp;rsquo;t back down — here&amp;rsquo;s how it could affect sales Nordstrom is refusing to ditch Ivanka Trump&amp;rsquo;s brand — and people are furious More than a third of consumers say they&amp;rsquo;re unlikely to shop at retailers selling Trump products Ivanka Trump has been hit with one of the biggest criticisms plaguing her father The anti-Trump boycott of 70 retailers won&amp;rsquo;t back down — here&amp;rsquo;s how it could affect sales Macy&amp;rsquo;s is under pressure to drop Ivanka Trump Uber CEO backs out of joining Trump&amp;rsquo;s business council Since the election, 3,600 Trump-branded products have been dropped from online stores Another major retailer just dropped Trump-brand merchandise An anti-Trump movement is doubling down on its boycott of Amazon on Prime Day (AMZN)  Bust  It&amp;rsquo;s been about a week since the official election results have come out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Ads Spotted on Fox</title>
      <link>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/other_ads_spotted_on_fox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 13:45:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/other_ads_spotted_on_fox/</guid>
      <description>dl {border-bottom:10px solid #ececec;padding-bottom:40px;} dt {font-weight:600;margin-right:10px;} dt:nth-child(1), dt:nth-child(3) {float:left;} h2 {padding-top:20px;}  This part of the site was created during the Roy Moore scandal in order to track advertisers that appear on Fox News, which &amp;ldquo;at the time&amp;rdquo; was promoting a skewed narrative designed to politicize the issue of sexual harassment and undermine Moore&amp;rsquo;s accusers. For example, it ran a story entitled &amp;ldquo;Roy Moore accuser worked for Clinton campaign&amp;rdquo; and failed to mention that the company of the accuser in question &amp;ldquo;a sign language interpretation service&amp;rdquo; had also provided services to Republican campaigns and candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Companies On Our Radar</title>
      <link>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/other_companies_on_our_radar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 13:45:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/other_companies_on_our_radar/</guid>
      <description>dt {font-weight:600;color:#777;} h2 {color:#333;padding-top:20px;} dl {border-bottom:10px solid #ececec;padding-bottom:40px;}  Note: this is the FYI area of the #GrabYourWallet site, which is a separate area from the main boycott portion. As of February 2018, companies with corporate PACs that have recently contributed money to NRA-approved U.S. senators and/or their campaigns are included in this portion of the list. These companies are in italic and bold.
 AARP American Express Amway Andrew Marc (clothing) AT&amp;amp;T Amazon Autozone Bank of America Blackstone Strategic Partners Blackrock Financial Planning BNSF Boeing Boston Consulting Group (Consulting) BP Corporation Calvin Klein Carl&amp;rsquo;s Junior Caterpillar Charles Schwab Chase Chewy Chevron Cigna Cinemark Citigroup Cleveland Clinic Coca Cola Cole Haan Corning Covington Dana Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/safe_companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 13:45:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/safe_companies/</guid>
      <description>h2 {color:#333;border-top:5px solid #ececec;padding-top:20px;}  Table of Content
 Shop These 100% Trump-Free Alternatives Trump-Free Online Shoe Sites &amp;ldquo;Brave Brands&amp;rdquo; Kindle &amp;amp; Audible Alternatives Amazon Fire Alternatives Trump-Free Wedding Registry Options Places to Donate Shoes or Clothes Alternatives to Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Streaming Movies / TV Shows  Please note: the companies listed below are NOT on the boycott list. They are presented as ALTERNATIVES to the companies on the boycott list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Companies Have Been Dropped</title>
      <link>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/which_companies_have_been_dropped/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 13:45:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grabyourwallet.org/which_companies_have_been_dropped/</guid>
      <description>.content  ul  li  a {font-weight:600;} .content  ul  li {margin-bottom:30px;} dt {font-weight:600;color:#777;margin-right:10px;} dt {float:left;} h2 {color:#333;} h3 {padding-top:20px;} dl {border-bottom:10px solid #ececec;padding-bottom:40px;} main  div  ul  li  a {font-size:1.5rem;display:block;border-bottom:2px solid #cecece;text-decoration:none;margin:40px 0 10px;padding-bottom:10px;}   Trump-Related Drops  Shoes.com Bellacor Jenny Craig Wayfair Zulily RueLaLa Kawasaki USA Uber The Honest Company Tyra Beauty Jet Carnival Corporation Nordstrom Nordstrom Rack Gilt Kmart Sears ShopStyle Lorissa&amp;rsquo;s Kitchen LA Clippers QVC Neiman Marcus Tesla / SpaceX Disney Merck Under Armour Intel Pepsi GM IBM 3M Campbell&amp;rsquo;s Soup American Cancer Society Cleveland Clinic American Red Cross Susan G.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>